const monthsToNumbers = [
    {
        question: 'January',
        answers: ['1'],
    },
    {
        question: 'February',
        answers: ['2'],
    },
    {
        question: 'March',
        answers: ['3'],
    },
    {
        question: 'April',
        answers: ['4'],
    },
    {
        question: 'May',
        answers: ['5'],
    },
    {
        question: 'June',
        answers: ['6'],
    },
    {
        question: 'July',
        answers: ['7'],
    },
    {
        question: 'August',
        answers: ['8'],
    },
    {
        question: 'September',
        answers: ['9'],
    },
    {
        question: 'October',
        answers: ['10'],
    },
    {
        question: 'November',
        answers: ['11'],
    },
    {
        question: 'December',
        answers: ['12'],
    },
];

export default monthsToNumbers;
